

L Tenzil

Web & Product Developer

Senior Ruby, Ruby on Rails. Junior Elixir & Phoenix developer.

7 years of experience in developing robust Ruby on Rails applications with Postgresql, Javascript and Deployment activities. Posses good communication, analytical and problem solving skills.

Built few personal products in my own time, do have a plan releasing it in a while.









■ Itenzil@gmail.com

Project Timeline

American worldwide provider of patent risk management services. in Pramati Technologies.

Learn | Interscholastic Education, Made Easy. in Webonise Lab

Union Cloud - Managing student's society or club online. in **Arrk Solutions**

Personal Products

Oogway, a social learning platform. Now development is on

Challenge Accepted, platform for friendly challenges. Now development is on hold. Feature video

Skills

Ruby

Fell in love with Ruby in 2014, Since then working in it.

Database

Postgresql

HTML, Javascript and CSS Worked on Jquery, HAML and SLIM template engines.

Project Management Tools

Have used Rally, JIRA, Trello

LEARNING CURRENTLY

Post ruby, elixir stole my heart with its elegent style and pace. Building pet projects and learning it.

Progressive Web Apps(PWA)

Used to achieve mobile app like feel and offline experience.

GIT, SVN

Ruby on Rails

AWS Services

UI frameworks

Version Control

pet projects in version 6

The Rails for elixir, using it to build web applications.

Zurb Foundation, Semantic UI, Bootstrap

Simple Notification Service, a notification service provided by AWS for Email, HTTPS, SMS and other services.

Have extensively worked on ROR projects, from version 3 to 5, Doing some

EC2, ELB, S3, Route53, SES, Involved in deployment activities

IN THE PIPELINE

Frontend Frameworks

Vuejs

Employment

Pramati Technologies, Imaginea

- * Senior Development Engineer
- American worldwide provider of patent risk management services.
- From September 2017 to March 23 2020.
- Chennai, TamilNadu, India

Webonise Lab

- * Senior Software Developer
- Learn | Interscholastic Education, Made Easy.
- From May 2016 to September 2017.
- Pune, Maharastra, India

- * Software Developer
- Learn | Interscholastic Education, Made Easy.
- From May 2015 to May 2016.
- Pune, Maharastra, India

Arrk Solutions

- * Software Engineer
- Union Cloud Managing student's society or club online.
- From February 2014 to April 2015.
- NaviMumbai, Maharastra, India

R Roles & Responsibilities

In these 7 years, I have taken few roles and responsibilities as follows:

Team management, Mentoring and Grooming team members.

Story estimation, Analysis, Ideation, Development activities and Fixing Bugs

Refactoring and Support Activities

Deployment and Cultural Activities

Education

PSN College of Engineering and Technology

- * Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), B.Tech[I.T]
- 2008-2012
- Tirunelveli, TamilNadu, India

St. John's Higher Secondary School

- * Higher Secondary Mathematics and Biology
- **=** 2006-2008
- Tirunelveli, TamilNadu, India

Awards & Achievements





Gold Class Award

Hobbies & Interests















Music

■ Movies & Web Series

Table Tennis

Hiking & Trekking